freedirectorysubmit.com 2017-12-11

# Free Directory Submit | - Privacy Policy

## FreeDirectorySubmit.com Privacy Policy

We restrict the use of personal information to only what is required to supply the service. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact our support staff by using the contact us form available on-site. Please note that as a web and business directory this site contains links to other sites. FreeDirectorySubmit is not in any way responsible for the privacy practices, privacy statements, or content of these other sites.

### Information Collection

We do not collect personally identifying information from users of our site unless the user explicitly and intentionally enters it, or attempts to violate our security systems. FreeDirectorySubmit is the only owner of the information collected on the web sites listed. We offer users the ability to enter personally identifying information at several different points on our web site.

### Delivery of Services

We collect information about servers connected to the IPs or URLs given by the users during the listing process. IP's and URL's are checked to verify users authority to do invasive port scanning, and/or vulnerability and penetration testing. No invasive data is collected until the user requests it and is verified as having proper authority to request the data to be collected. We only collect information that can be accessed from the internet about users computer(s) we do not install software on the users computers. We store information that we collect through your online listing/s which creates a profile for our users. A listing is then stored as information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing and services preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the user's personally identifiable information to provide other interested parties relevant information about the users listed site. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions for our listed clients.

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use only session cookies and do not use persistent cookies. A session cookie simply terminates once users close the browser.

### Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information or listing circumstances changes (such as website details, email etc), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users. personally identifiable information. This can usually be done by contacting us using the contact form available on-site.

### Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy statement including privacy, information use, collection, or security, please contact us using the contact for available on-site.

Thank you for submitting your website and information to FreeDirectorySubmit.com,  
The FreeDirectorySubmit.com staff.
